smartsuggestor.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Think Tank Labs, LLC’s (“Think Tank”, “we”, or “us”) Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of information that may be collected by Think Tank anytime you interact with us, such as when you visit the website smartusggestor.com (the “Site”) or when you use the Think Tank software known as the Smart Suggestor (the “Software”). 

Please take a moment to read the following Privacy Policy to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. 

If you choose to visit the Site or use the Software, your visit and Software use, and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Site’s [End User License Agreement](http://www.smartsuggestor.com/eula.html), including limitations on damages and jurisdiction of disputes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at privacy@smartsuggestor.com or write to us at: 

Think Tank Labs, LLC  
Privacy Policy – Smart Suggestor  
620 Newport Center Drive Ste 1100   
Newport Beach, CA 92660 

In addition, if you require support regarding the Site you can contact through the Site at the following link: [here](http://www.smartsuggestor.com/support.html).   

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 31, 2013. 

We may modify this Privacy Policy, for example, to reflect changes to the law or changes to our Site or Software. We will post notice of modifications to this Privacy Policy on this page and we will post notice of modifications within the Software and obtain your informed consent before making any material changes.  Your use of the Software and the Site after such modification constitutes your acceptance of such changes to this Privacy Policy.   
**Why we collect your information**  
We use non-personally identifiable data collected from users of the Software and the Site in order to: ****

  * To improve the quality and functionality of the Site, enhance your experience, create new services (including customized services), change/cancel existing content and services, or for other internal and statistical purposes.
  * To present you relevant content, marketing materials and advertisements, by analyzing your interests from the web pages you visit and online services that you use.
  * To provide you with support and handle inquires.
  * To enforce our terms of use and/or EULA.
  * To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies as required.
  * To conduct surveys and market researches.

We may use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information about the website’s use and share, publish, post, disseminate, transmit or otherwise communicate or make available such information, to suppliers, business partners, sponsors, affiliates and any other third party, at our sole discretion ****  
**What information we collect from you -** **Cookies and other technologies**  
We collect or receive information about you when you interact with us.  For example, in order to provide you with customer service, if necessary.  As is standard practice on many websites, we use "cookies" and other technologies to help us understand which parts of the Site are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. You are always free to disable cookies on your browser. Please note that certain features of the Site and Software may not be available once cookies are disabled.    
As is true of most websites and downloadable software applications, we also gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Site and Software, to track users' movements around the Site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  
We do not obtain information about you from third party sources to supplement our information.   
**Sharing of Your Information**

We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties.  We may share your information with third parties to provide products and services you have requested or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

Your information may be accessed and disclosed in response: to lawful governmental requests or legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena), in other circumstances in which we have a good faith belief that a crime has been or is being committed by a user of the Software, that an emergency exists that poses a threat to the safety of you or another person, when necessary either to protect the rights or property of Think Tank, or for us to render the service you have requested.

Our business partners will receive data about you such as the searches you have conducted on certain search engines, but our business partners will not receive information that personally identifies you. We use this information to provide you with the most relevant advertisements only. 

We may use also agents and contractors in order to help operate the Site and Software. Their use of information is limited to the operation of the Site and the Software including hosting the Site and these agents and contractors will not receive information that personally identifies you.

In the event that ownership of the Site or Software was to change as a result of a merger, acquisition, or transfer to another company, your information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your information, you will be provided notice about the changes.

**Accessing and controlling the integrity of your information**

You may remove the Software at any time as described in the End User License Agreement.  We may retain your information in conformance with our data retention policy, under which we may retain such information to comply with laws, prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. 

If you would like access to your personal information to correct, update, or delete it, please contact us as described below:

Think Tank Labs, LLC  
Privacy Policy – Smart Suggestor  
620 Newport Center Drive Ste 1100   
Newport Beach, CA 92660   
privacy[at]smartsuggestor[dot]com

**How we protect your information**  
We take precautions - including administrative, technical, and physical measures - to safeguard your information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction; however, no method  of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.  We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Kids**  
In order to use our Software you must represent and warrant that you are over the age of 18.  Children under the age of 18 are not eligible to use the Software and must not attempt to download or use the Software. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any person who is under the age of 18 or allow them to use the Software. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 18, we will delete this information as quickly as possible.

**Links to other sites**  
Our Site and Software contains links to, and allow you to share content on, third party websites and services. The fact that we link to a website or service or allow you to share content on them is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

**International users**  
The Site and Software is hosted in the United States. If you access the Site or Software from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site or Software, you are transferring your Information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. Additionally, you understand that your Information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing Information may be less stringent than in your country.
